# Ali Demirbaş

# Software Developer

Address Istanbul, 34, 34480

**Phone** +90-542-207-0662

E-mail ali.ds@outlook.com.tr

**LinkedIn** https://linkedin.com/in/alidemirbas

**Github** https://github.com/alidemirbas

Hey this is the project guy!

He likes teamwork and is extremely adaptable.

He writes code that everyone can understand.

Respectful, humble and self-confident. But his real talents and skills are revealed when he takes on big responsibilities on projects.

He brings out "the best" together with his teammates who help and support him.

The projects in his experience are proof of that.

You can trust this guy who adapts quickly to new technologies and always gets the job done perfectly!

## **Skills**

C#	Excellent
.Net Framework, .Net Core, .Net 5, .Net 6	Excellent
ASP.NET MVC, ASP.NET Web API, ASP.NET Core	Excellent
Object Oriented Programming	Excellent
JIRA ,Agile, Scrum	
TCP/IP, Websocket	Very Good
MSSQL, Postgre SQL, Mongo DB, Redis	Very Good
Javascript, Jquery, Telerik, Devexpress	Very Good
ADO.NET	Excellent
Dapper ORM	Excellent
Azure	Very Good
7.2010	Good

Docker

Wery Good

MVC, MVVM, Design Patterns

Excellent

Micro Service Architecture

Very Good

RabbitMQ

Very Good

# **Work History**

## 2022-02 - Project Manager

2022-10 Kumport Liman Hizmetleri ve Loj. San. ve Tic. A.Ş., İstanbul, Istanbul

## **Projects:**

## **USER MANAGEMENT SYSTEM PROJECT**

## Description:

it is both an Application management and User management project developed to be used in all projects of the company.

## Technologies:

- -.NET 6
- GIT
- ASP.NET Core Identity
- Identity Server 4
- OpenIdConnect
- JWT
- Jquery, Bootstrap
- MSSQL

#### Tasks:

- All BE, FE and Service development processes

## **KUMPORT TEMPLATE**

## Description:

It is a template project developed for the architecture to be used in the new projects of the company.

- -.NET 6
- GIT
- ASP.NET Core
- ASP.NET Core Web API

- Jquery, Bootstrap - MSSQL
- Tasks:

- All BE, FE and Service development processes

#### KUMPORT FRAMEWORK

## Description:

The libraries developed to be used in all the projects of the company.

## Technologies:

-.NET 6

#### Tasks:

- All BE development processes

#### JIRA INTEGRATION

#### Description:

it is an integration system developed to manage all requests in the company.

## Technologies:

- -.NET 4.5
- -GIT
- -Windows Services

#### Tasks:

- All BE and Service development processes

## 2022-09 - Full Stack Developer

2022-10 Asis Elektronik ve Bilişim Sistemleri A.Ş., İstanbul, Istanbul

#### Projects:

#### ELECTRONIC TRASPORTATITION PORTAL (Smart City Card)

## Description:

It is the electronic transportation and payment system and smart city card project used in forty cities of Turkey. It allows tracking the payment transactions of the bus and smart cards used in urban transportation.

- ASP.NET Core
- EntityFramework
- Javascript, Jquery, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap

- Postgre SQL
- WebSocket
- Redis
- RabbitMa

- All BE and FE tasks

## 2019-04 - Full Stack Developer

2021-04 Rasyotek İnsan Kaynakları Bilişim A.Ş., İstanbul, Istanbul

## **Projects:**

#### SUPERPORTAL.COM

#### Description:

it is the digital platform of robotic enterprise solutions. For more information; https://www.rasyotek.com.tr/super-portal-nedir

Sub-projects I have been tasked with:

- Personnel Incentive System (Personel Teşvik Sistemi) link: "https://pts.superportal.com"
- Digital Automation System Technologies (Dijital Otomasyon Sistem Teknolojileri) link: "https://dost.superportal.com"
- Rayotek Academy (Rasyotek Akademi) link: "https://akademi.superportal.com"
- Location Analysis (Lokasyon Analizi) link: "https://akademi.superportal.com"
- Digital-Personal Data Protection Law (Dijital-Kişisel Verileri Koruma Kanunu) link: "https://kvkk.superportal.com"
- Bordrotek

## Technologies:

- Docker
- Microservices
- Kubernates
- GIT
- AZURE
- CI/CD pipelines
- JIRA
- ASP.NET Core
- NET 5
- Jauery, Bootstrap, DevExpress
- MSSQL

#### Tasks:

- All BE, FE and Service development processes

## 2018-01 - Full Stack Developer

2018-04 COLIN'S Eroğlu Holding, İstanbul, Istanbul

## **Projects:**

## ESCM (Eroğlu Supply Chain Management)

## Description:

It is a logistics project where products can be tracked from the producer to the end consumer.

## Technologies:

- ASP.NET Core MVC
- Entityframework
- Telerik Kendo and Its Reporting Integration Services
- MSSQL

#### Tasks:

- BE and FE tasks from trello task pool

## 2016-10 - Full Stack Developer

2017-10 OFIX OFIS MALZEMELERI A.Ş. (Ofix.com), İstanbul, Istanbul

## **Projects:**

## HIPPOSOFT E-COMMERCE WEB SERVICE

## Description:

It is a service project that offers e-commerce data and features to marketplaces.

## Technologies:

- WCF (REST and SOAP)
- Dapper ORM
- MSSQL

#### Tasks:

- Developing service endpoints

#### OFIX.COM

## Description:

ofix.com is the e-commerce website of Ofix Ofis Malzemeleri A.Ş.

#### Technologies:

- ASP.NET MVC

- Jquery, Bootstrap
- Hipposoft Web Service

- Hipposoft web service integration
- FE tasks

#### <u>IYZICO PAYMENT SERVICE INTEGRATION</u>

## Description:

Integration of lyzico payment gateway system, which provides services in payment systems, to ofix.com.

## Techologies:

- ASP.NET WebAPI

#### Tasks:

- All integration tasks

#### MASTERPASS PAYMENT SERVICE INTEGRATION

## Description:

With the payment system offered by Mastercard, the integration of the service to ofix.com, which enables users to save their credit/debit card information to the Mastercard infrastructure and to use their registered cards for payment transactions.

## Technologies:

- ASP.NET WebAPI

#### Tasks:

- All integration tasks

## **E-INVOICE SERVICE INTEGRATION**

## Description:

A web service that allows invoicing the waybills of the collected orders, sending them to the Revenue Administration, saving the information and files, and taking the printout automatically and also mvc project with a CMS.

- ADO.NET
- ASP.NET WebAPI
- ASP.NET MVC
- Jquery
- MSSQL

- Developing all integration process
- Developing invoice contents and files management system.

## WAYBILL AUTOMATION SYSTEM

Description: It is the sub-module of the E-invoice service that automatically prints out the waybills of the collected orders.

## Technologies:

- ADO.NET
- ASP.NET WebAPI
- Windows Form Application
- MSSQL

#### Tasks:

- All development process

#### E-LEDGER INTEGRATION SERVICE

Description: It is the sub-module of the E-invoice service, which enables the e-ledgers of the months to be sent to the Revenue Administration.

## Technologies:

- ADO.NET
- ASP.NET WebAPI
- MSSQL

#### Tasks:

-All development process

## 2015-09 - Full Stack Developer

2016-09 PikselNet Bilişim Hizmetleri, İstanbul, Istanbul

## **Projects:**

## **PIKSOLA**

## Description:

Piksola is a e-commerce framework including content management system.

- EntityFramework
- ADO.NET

- ASP.NET MVC
- MVVM Pattern (Telerik Kendo)
- Javascript, Jquery, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap
- MSSQL

- Piksola Lightweight ORM library
- Filtering, Sorting, Paging, Grouping library
- CMS developing
- All BE and FE tasks

#### **NEWAL.COM.TR**

## Description:

Newal.com.tr is a multilanguage catalog website that uses Piksola framework. link: "http://newal.com.tr/en"

## Technologies:

- ASP.NET framework MVC
- Javascript, Jquery, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap

#### Tasks:

- Developing website by using Piksola framework

## **Education**

2008-01 - Master of Science: Chemistry

2012-09 Dumlupınar University Faculty of Arts And Sciences - Kütahya

# **Additional Information**

#### **MY LIBRARIES**

#### P.ErrorManagement

#### Description:

It is a library that aims to carry out all error management in projects from a single point. Used with P.LogManagement, it also provides both catching and logging of errors.

#### Technologies:

- .Net Core
- .Net Standart
- ASP.NET MVC Core

## P.LogManagement

## Description:

It undertakes the task of logging in projects and ensures that the logs are executed from a single point. Provides options to save to file or save to Database.

## Technologies:

- .Net Core
- .Net Standart

## P.IOC

## Description:

It is the IOC Container developed for "Dependency Inversion" and "Dependency Injection". Its difference from similar libraries and the advantage it provides is that it realizes the type of objects to be registered with a JSON configuration file.

## Technologies:

- -.Net Core
- .Net Standart

## P.ObjectMapping

## Description:

It is a library that enables data to be mapped. Its difference from similar libraries and the advantage it provides is that it has a simpler use/syntax and is lighter.

## Technologies:

- .Net Core
- .Net Standart

## P.FGSP

## Description:

It is a library that allows building IQueryable objects for Filtering, Grouping, Sorting, Paging operations.

## Technologies:

- .Net Core
- .Net Standart
- -.Net Core
- .Net Standart

# Languages

# Interests

Electronic
Basketball
Swimming
Lying on the beach and having a nice drink:)